Guide to the Margaret Wylie papers, 1926-1963.
Wylie, Margaret papers, 1926-1963.
- Series I. Cornell Study Clubs
  - Erie County and Buffalo
    - Mrs. Milligan, Buffalo, 1933-1936 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Mrs. J.H. Baker, St. Paul's Parish Mothers'Club, 1934-1936 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Mrs. C.L. Baltz, North Main Home Bureau, 1934-1938 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Mrs. H.E. Bradway, Buffalo, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Mrs. John Newton, Buffalo, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Mrs. Wilbur West, Buffalo, 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Mrs. C.H. Kenny, Kenmore, Buffalo City, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Mrs. John Nantz, Kenmore Pre-School Child Study Group, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Mrs. W. Lewin, Buffalo, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Mrs. J.C. Stewart, North Main study group, 1936-1939 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Mrs. Katharine N. Britt, County Leader-short course, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Mrs. C. Cadmen, Buffalo, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Mrs. C.S. Kenworthy, North Park Mothers' Club, Kenmore, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Mrs. Ormal H. Christie, Personality Study Club, group A, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Mrs. Leonard Rautenberg, Kenmore, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Mrs. J.P. Cotter, South Park, Buffalo, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Mrs. Charles S. Freeman, Snyder, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Mrs. George Hudson, Snyder, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Mrs. D.J. McCarthy, Buffalo, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Mrs. J. Roach, Buffalo, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Mrs. Clarence Stisser, Snyder Child Study Club, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Mrs. Eugene Sullivan, North Oak, Buffalo, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Dr. Mazie Wagner, University of Buffalo, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. R.V. Woodbury, Kenmore, "Getting On with Others", 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. J. Costello, Kenmore, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Richard Eaton: Group I, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Richard Eaton: Group II, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. Richard Eaton: Group III, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Howard Gibson, Ken-Del unit, "Parent-Adolescent Conflict", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. E.H. Johnson, Ken-Del unit, "Keeping Mentally Well", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. George C. Kratzer, Kenmore, "Family Relationships", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. W.H. Lynch, Kenmore, "Guidance Through School Years", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. Peter J. Murrett, Kenmore, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. R. Nauth, Kensington, "Understanding the Middle Years", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Leonard Rautenberg, Kenmore, "Personality", 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. Howard L. Wright, Kenmore, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. Arthur G. Maddigan, Bennett Group, Buffalo, 1931-1940 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. E. Piper, Cornell Child Study Club, Buffalo, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. M. Hausauer, A.A.U.W. group, Buffalo, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. Nelson N. Beale, High Street group, 1933-1939 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. A. Maddigan, Buffalo, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mrs. E.W. Howell, Central Presbyter Church, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. Helen Kinsman, First M.E. Church Mothers' Club, 1934-1937 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. Louis B. Thornton, Delaware Ave. Baptist, 1934-1937 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. James C. Stewart, Adolescent Study Group, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. Whitney Hale, Elmwood School, 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. C.J. Fox, Jefferson-Humboldt Unit, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. Clarence Preston, North Collins, NY study club, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - study club, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. E. J. Beach, Williamsville, NY study club, 1931-1935 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. W. L. Clarck, West Falls, NY study club, 1931-1939 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Blanche Willett, Lawtons, NY study club, 1932-1940 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Untitled, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. S. A. Gibson, Synder, NY study club, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1935-1939 (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
    - Mrs. John S. Turner, Wanakah, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Ruth Lane, Sardinia, NY study club, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. John Herman, Orchard Park, Chairman, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Mrs. Jack O'Bannon, Williamsville, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Mrs. Natalie D. Crowe, Williamsville, NY Study Club and county leader, 1938-1940 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. A. Zimmerman, Williamsville, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. Mary A. Switzer, 210 Pearl St., Buffalo 2, 1942-1944 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Home Bureau meetings, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - County Leader: Mrs. Natalie Crowe, 113 Monroe Dr., Williamsville, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - County Leader: Mrs. T.H. Welch, 20 S. Cayuga St., Williamsville, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. George Finch, Alden, NY, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Helen Hoover, Clarence, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - 3 Beats Study Club, Clarence, NY, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Clarence Center, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - E. Aurora, NY, 1943-1945 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Pauline Walker, Willow St., E. Aurora, NY, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. Crystal Warren, Hamburg, NY, 1942-1944 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. Lloyd S. Behrns, 29 Pleasant Ave., Hamburg, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Koenig Road Study Club, Mrs. Edward Baxter, Tonawanda (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. Annie Taylor, Lawtons, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. Henry McCaskey, Orchard Park, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. John R. Armstrong, 56 Norwood Ave., Snyder, NY, 1940-1943 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Cornell Study Group, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Tonawanda Study Club, Grace Methodist Church, Mothers Guild, Erie; Mrs. Albert Hubman, 96 Williams St., Tonawanda, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Erie, Mother Hubbard, Mrs. Elizabeth Pawemore, 14 Arondale Rd., Williamsville, 1940-1945 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Child Study, Williamsville, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Daniel Lanning, Harris Hill, Wildwood Drive, Williamsville, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Series XVI. Franklin County
    - Miss Eloise Irish, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Miss Eloise Irish, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Local Leader Training Meeting, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Bombay Study Club, Mrs. F.J. Shields, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Malone Study Club, Mrs. Don E. Huddleston, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Odessa Dow, Court House, Malone, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Family Life Leader - Mrs. Ada M. Lester, Rte. 3, Malone, NY, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Russell Newell, Jr., 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Brookside Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Elwood Belnap, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. A.E. Martin, Gabriels, NY, 1940-1941, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Fulton County
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Genesee County
    - Genesee County - Batavia, Oakfield, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Genesee County - Batavia, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. Esther Bushey, Batavia, NY (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Batavia, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Loraine Hint, Oakfield, NY study club, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. Jean Rich, Oakfield, NY study club, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. Mae Brundage, Oakfield, NY study club, 1933-1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1940 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. W. M. Coward, So. Byron, NY study club, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. Stella Crocker, Le Roy, NY study club, 1934-1936 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Chester Churchill, Basom, NY study club, 1934-1937 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. Rockwood, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. C. A. Chapman, Le Roy, NY study club, 1935-1937 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. Marian Hews, Batavia, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Mr. Entorf's Material, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Mrs. H. Vanderhoof, Elba, NY study club, 1937-1939 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. Harris Gardner, Alexander, NY study club, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Wilber Chase, Batavia, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. Claire Ballard, Batavia, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Earl Connolly, Oakfield, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Rhoda Mekeel, Home Demonstration Agent, 33 State St., Batavia, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Home Bureau Unit MJGS, 1941-1944 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Oakfield Mothers' Club, Bernice Kriner, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Tonawanda Gahunda Study Club, Batavia, NY - Chairman Mrs. Ethel Hall, 5 East Ave. (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - S. Alabama Study Club - Mrs. Metta Cooper, Oakfield, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Greene County
    - Untitled, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Untitled, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Herkimer County
    - Herkimer, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Miss Grace H. Smith, Home Demonstration Agent, 1932-1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Untitled, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Philip Watts, Little Falls, NY mother's club, 1937-1938 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Mr. Entorf, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Local Leader Training Meeting, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Home Demonstration Agent P.O. Bldg., Herkimer, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1945 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Mrs. Vedder Dorn, Main St., Mohawk, NY (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Jefferson County
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1940 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Ella Thomas, Rodman, NY study club, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Anita Durand, Chairman, Watertown, NY study club, 1934-1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. A. S. Yates, Watertown, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Marie Laird, County Leader, Watertown, NY, 1937-193 8 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Mr.Endorfs material, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Home Bureau Meetings, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, Federal Bldg., Watertown, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Philadelphia Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. William Andrews (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Watertown Child Study - Mrs. Carl Shippee, 712 S. Hamilton St., Watertown, NY (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Family Life Study Club - Mrs. Marion Bauer, Watertown, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - West Carthage Child Study - Mrs. Andrew Hill, West Carthage, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - St. Lawrence Family Life Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Ethel Mitchel, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lewis County
    - Miss Clarance Cookingham, Home Demonstration Agent, 1932-1940 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. C. S. Shuman, Leader at Large, 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. Elizabeth Gernard, Chairman, Greig study club, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Dorothy Bradley, Home Demonstration Agent, Lowville, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Glenfield Family Life Study Club - Mrs. John Clark, Glenfield, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Livingston County
    - Mt. Morris, NY, 1930-1937 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Helen Stein, Home Demonstration Agent, Mount Norris, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Home Bureau Unit, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. Stuart S. Nicholson, 41 Murray St., Mr. Morris, NY, 1942-1944 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Mrs. Arlene Kennedy, 145 Main St., Mt. Morris, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Madison County
    - Madison County - Hamilton, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Madison County - Wampersville, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Wampsville, NY, 1930-1937 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. Otis P. Marshall, Munnsville, NY study club, 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Mrs. J. Roy Clarke Cazenovia, NY study club, 1931-1934 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Wanye Benedict, county leader, 1931-193 7 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. Frank Marshall, county leader, 1931-1937 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. Beecher, Hamilton, NY study club, 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. Winfred Tyler, Oneida, NY study club, 1931-1940 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Raymony Burdick, Brookfield, NY study club, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's material, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Mrs. S.W. Beekman, Oneida, NY study club, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. J. B. Cronk, Lebanon, NY study club, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Mrs. J. LaSalle, Georgetown, NY study club, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Eathel Lamb, Hubbardsville, NY study club, 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Home Bureau Unit Meetings, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. Charles Edkins, Hamilton, NY, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Care of Children at Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mrs. Lucy Usher, Earlville, NY study club, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Mrs. Glenn Lyman, Munnsville NY study club, 1939-1941 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Rachel Merritt, Home Demonstration Agent, Wompsville Court House, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Home Bureau, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - County Leader for Madison County, 1940-1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Care of children at meetings, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Brookfield - Mrs. Herman J. Palmes, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Young Mothers' Club of Munnsville, NY, 1941-1943 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mrs. Roselyn Frost, Munnsville, NY, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Munnsville Child Study - Mrs. Donald Greene, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Oneida Child Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Hugh Malone, 350 Broad St., Oneida, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Herbert Simpkins, 98 Senaca Ave., Oneida Castle, NY, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Monroe County and Rochester
    - Monroe County - Rochester, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Monroe County - Rochester, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. Mabel H. Ellsworth, Churchville, NY, 1931-1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. B. Maxfield, Pittsford, NY, 1931-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. C.H. Palmer, Webster, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. Walter Quinn, Hilton, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Mrs. Clarence Tobey, Pittsford, NY, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Miss Georgie Watkins and Miss Searles, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, Monroe County, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Frederick Dalzell, Coldwater, NY, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. Edward Piper, Henrietta, NY, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. George Symonds, Brighton Station, Rochester, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mrs. Everett Chaffee, Coldwater, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Monroe County, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. Francis Corkhill, Fairport, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Mrs. Alma Fewster, Webster, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. Fred Kesel, Henrietta, NY, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Monroe County, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. M.C. Burritt, Hilton, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Mr. Entorf's materials, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mrs. Merton Colby, Spencerport, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Mr. Entorf's materials, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Louise Root, Webster, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Mrs. Edward Cissel, Brighton, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. George Finn, Webster, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Mrs. Milton Hallauer, Webster, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. B.H. Sage, Churchville, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Monroe County: Rochester, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Mrs. Gifford Bloomer, Rochester City Leader, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Neal F. Clement, N. Presbyterian Church, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. Lewis Edgarton, Seneca School, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Mrs. Francis Guthrie, Rochester, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Dr. Piedmore Club, Rochester, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Mrs. Judson Scott, Child Psychology Group, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Mrs. E.H. Walker, Rochester City Leader, 1931-1937 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. Reid Weidman, Rochester, NY, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Dorothy Bloomer, Study Course for Parents, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Mrs. G.M. Denison, Church of the Master, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. G. Sackett, Chamber of Commerce meetings, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1933-1940 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Mrs. Reinhard Bretz, Rochester City Leader, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. W.J. Hagstrom, Chamber of Commerce, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Jane Hagstrom, Chamber of Commerce: "School Child" study course, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Mrs. Henry L. Hudson, Irondequoit, Rochester, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. Fred B. Odell, Rochester, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Mrs. E.H. Walker, Home Bureau study club, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Mrs. J.H. Wright, "Preschool Child" study club, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Mrs. H.P. Heislein, Rochester, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. Jordan Ross, Rochester, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's material, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Mrs. Eloise Howarth, Home Bureau study club, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Mrs. E.H. Walker, Rochester, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Frances E.W. Searles, Home Demonstration Agent, 524 Mt. Hope Ave., Rochester 7, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Home Bureau file, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Family Life Leader: Mr. Glenn Lewis, 49 Pearwood Rd., Rochester (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - County Leader: Mrs. E.H. Walker, 25 Leander Rd., Rochester, 1940-1942 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - County Leader: Mrs. M.C. Burritt, Hilton, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Local leader training meetings, Monroe County (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Brockport Parents' Club - Mrs. Frank A. Hixson, 34 Kenyon St., Brockport, NY, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Mrs. B. Sage, Churchville, NY, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - East Rochester Study Club - Mrs. Harriet Greeley, 124 E. Ivy St., E. Rochester, NY, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Cornell Family Life Study Program, Chairman Mrs. Leroy Morlock, E. Rochester; Mrs. Frances R. George, Secretary, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - East Rochester - Mrs. Betty Mousso, 311 W. Filbert St., 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - East Rochester Homemakers' Club - Mrs. Edgar W. Blick, 11 Lake Crescent Dr., East Rochester, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Hamlin Child Study Group I, Chairman Mrs. George Sigler, Hamlin; Mrs. Adrian Nichols, Secretary, 1940-1945 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Hamlin Child Study Group II, Fern Roth, Hamlin, NY (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Small Fry Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Stuart Kintz; Marie Lutz, Secretary, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Hilton Child Study Club I, Chairman Mrs. Charles Hiscolf, Lake Avenue, Parma; Mrs. Ed O. Gable, Secretary, 31 Hopen St., Parma, 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Hilton & 7:45 Study Club, Chairman Audrey Burritt; Bernice McMann, Secretary, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Penfield Child Study - Mrs. Joseph Momies, South Road, Penfield, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Mrs. Jensen, Pittsford, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Mrs. Ralph Johnson, Rochester, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Greece Child Study Club Group, Chairman Mrs. Robert Brightman; Mrs. Robert Schellberg, Secretary (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Henrietta Child Study Club - Mrs. John R. Van Ostrand, Henrietta, 1940-1945 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Irondequoit Study Club, Chairman Florence Katz, 15 Rowley St., Rochester, 1941-1945 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Koda-Vista Child Study - Mrs. John Pittman, 4 Acton St., Rochester 13, 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Suburban Child Study - Mrs. Crabill Waldron, 226 Orchard Park, Rochester, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Spencerport Parents' Discussion Club, Chairman Mrs. Harold Brown, 62 Bowery St., Spencerport, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Child Study, Chairman Mrs. Charles Knoll, 120 Coolidge Ave., Spencerport, 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Union Hill Study Club, Chairman Mrs. Raymond de Groot, Walworth, NY, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Webster Child Study Club No. 1, Chairman Mrs. Frank King, Webster, NY; Mrs. Nathaniel Perry, Secretary (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Webster Cornell Study Club, Mrs. P.J. Markell, Secretary (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Webster 4th Study Club Group, Chairman Marian Halbert, 62 Lapham Place, Webster, 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Webster Juniors' Mothers' Club, Chairman Mildred Van Hauten, Webster, NY; Mary K. Thomann, Secretary (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Urban Home Demonstration Agent, Miss Georgie Watkins, 150 N. Plymouth Ave., Rochester 6, 1940-1945 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Rochester City Home Bureau, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Pinnacle Child Study, Rochester City - Mrs. W.L. Taber, 36 Sonora Parkway, Rochester 7, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Monroe Child Study Club, Dec. 1, 1944; Chairman Mrs. Mollie Edelstein, 76 Coroman Terrace, Rochester, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. William Shea, 76 Merrill St., Rochester, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Arthur Taylor, 140 Weldon St., Rochester, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery County
    - Florence Titcomb, Home Demonstration Agent, 1943-1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Nassau County
    - Miss Florence Elrey, Mineola, NY, 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Rockwood's material, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mark Entorf's material, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Plainedge 4-H Club, Miss Anne Nassaro, Massapequa, NY, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Mr. Entorf's material, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. F.B. Taylor, W. Hempstead, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Home Demonstration Agent, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Mineola Study Club, Mrs. Ruth Campbell, Chairman, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Adelaide A. Bart, Court House Annex, Mineola, 1940-1945 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Home Bureau Report, 1943-1945 (Box 31, Folder 6)